JARRETÉ BARNETT

jy.barne

jy.barnett.io@gmail.com

C

(860) 614-9019

0

South Windsor, CT 06074

SKILLS

- CSS *****
- HTML *****
- SQL *****
- Git ★★★★★
- JavaScript ★★★★
- jQuery ★★★★
- Node.JS ★★★★
- React ★★★★
- Angular ★★★★
- Python ★★★★
- TypeScript ★★★★
- MongoDB ★★★
- Java ★★★

EDUCATION

University of Connecticut Storrs, CT • 07/2021

Certification: Full Stack Software Engineering

Central Connecticut State University

No Degree: Liberal Arts And General Studies Howell Cheney Technical High School

High School Diploma

CERTIFICATIONS

- UConn Coding Bootcamp
- Woz-U Application Development & Java Intensive Program

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An experienced Full Stack Software Engineer with background in building and maintaining server database applications, as well as client-side rendering for intuitive and responsive operating systems. Proven analytical and problem-solving abilities, supported by intensive training and verifiable certifications in software engineering and server-side computer sciences. Versatile working habits suited for either team-oriented or remote work conditions. Established track record for pursuing new challenges, including those involving opportunities to learn new technologies, languages, coding libraries and frameworks.

WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- jarretebarnett.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/jarretebarnett
- twitter.com/jarretedotio

WORK HISTORY

Turnberry Solutions - Software Engineer Associate I

St. Louis, MO • 05/2022 - Current

- Team is tasked with the responsibility of developing and refining Pay with Rewards features
 which offers users redemption rewards for eligible purchases.
- Make daily collaborative effort with product managers to designate top priority stories that can be managed and completed within current or upcoming sprints and iterations.
- Granted access to company repositories to modify applications and files as needed in order to
 optimize configuration and functionality, as well as eliminate any conflicting or obsolete code.
- Discuss best practices with team members when necessary, and commit to bi-weekly elaborations on anemic design stories.

William Raveis Real Estate Inc. - Licensed Real Estate Sales Associate

Avon, CT • 02/2020 - Current

- Manage a personal CRM database of customers and clients.
- Marketing for social media-centric engagement, reaching hundreds of active users monthly.
- Prospecting inventory for seller interest, market data, and inquiring customers planning to buy or
 rent

The Coder School - Instructional Coach

Glastonbury, CT • 11/2021 - 04/2022

- Provide support to students who are learning new software frameworks and languages.
- Relay notes of progress to both parents and internal administration.
- Refine students' skills in languages such as Python, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, etc.

Keller Williams Realty - Licensed Real Estate Sales Associate

Glastonbury, CT • 07/2019 - 01/2020

- Consultative experience with sellers inquiring about the marketability of their homes relative to
 existing inventory and proximity.
- Managed client expectations proceeding closings, as well as the technical diligence required to research relevant property data for customers.
- Closed over \$200,000 of volume within the first three months of licensure.
- Effectively closed home purchases expediently in a six-week timeframe.